Contactar

+573104403507 (Mobile) jlcaicedo@sjmedia.com.co

www.linkedin.com/in/jlcaicedo (LinkedIn)

www.josecaicedo.co (Personal) www.sjsocialmedia.com (Company)

Aptitudes principales

Online Advertising
Online Marketing
Mobile Marketing

Languages

Inglés (Professional Working)

Jose Luis Caicedo

Strategy and Planing Specialist on Digital Marketing San Francisco Bay Area

Extracto

Serial entrepreneur with strong leadership, innovation and strategic skills. Over 10 years of experience in tech industry. CO-Founder of SJ Social Media, a 100+ employees Marketing development company with over 1,000 corporate clients in 12 different countries.

Experiencia

SJ Social Media CMO noviembre de 2011 - Present

Miami/Fort Lauderdale y alrededores, Estados Unidos

I am in charge of the commercial part of the Digital Marketing Agency, developing strategies of online advertising, positioning in Google (SEO), design and communication on the Web, both for the company itself and for the client companies.

SJ Social Media Group Co-Founder noviembre de 2006 - Present

SJ Social Media is a Marketing Digital Studio with 100+ employees that has developed over 1800 digital projects which include, Web Sites, Ads online (SEM) and Positioning in Google (SEO).

Delivering world class quality products has been our mission and has given us the opportunity to work with companies in 12 countries around the world.

Jose Caicedo Vlog
Founder
enero de 2001 - Present
Miami/Fort Lauderdale y alrededores, Estados Unidos

Educación

Ludwig-Maximilians Universität München

Competitive Strategy · (2008 - 2008)

Florida International University

Master of Business Administration (MBA) · (2014 - 2015)

Miami Dade College

Bussines entrepreneurship, Business/Managerial Economics · (2010 - 2013)

Universidad de San Buenaventura

Economista · (2006 - 2011)

Massachusetts Institute of Technology

Computer Science and Engineering · (2001 - 2005)